# Bruna Kobay de Freitas

Fullstack Developer

Fullstack Developer with ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environments. I worked through 1000+ hours of bootcamp framework learning JavaScript, Node.Js, React.Js and Python. **Currently working as a** <u>freelancer</u>.

Brazilian (+55) 41 99778-7229 **brunakobay.com** linkedin.com/in/brunakobay/ **brunakobay@gmail.com** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## LabPlan, Laboratório de Planejamento Energético Researcher

MAR 2017 - DEC 2018

- Research and development of a methodology for automatic reconfiguration (self-healing) of medium voltage distribution networks applying Multiagent Systems concepts in the management of remote controlled equipment.
- Simulation and implementation of the initial methodology of automatic reconfiguration in Python.

## INESC P&D Brasil - LabPlan Junior Software Developer

JAN 2019 - Sept 2022

- Aid and study of methods for electric power planning.
- Development of automatic network recomposition software in Java.
- Maintenance and improvements of applications in C # and Python.

### **ACADEMIC EDUCATION**

# **Federal University of Santa Catarina,** Florianópolis Electrical Engineering

AUG 2011 - DEC 2018

One-year exchange program at the National University of Ireland, Galway.

#### **SKILLS**

React	••••
JavaScript	••••
HTML	••••
CSS	••••
C#	••••
C++	••••
Python	•••00
Django	••••

### **LANGUAGES**

English - Advanced